Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1104, Operators and Service Employees; Records apap121
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conventions and Seminars, 1978-2000; 5; 3.4 cubic ft.
  This series is arranged similarly to correspondence--the materials are grouped chronologically, then alphabetically within each year. There are brochures and other documents from many of the CWA annual conventions from the mid-1980s through 2000, but there are also many local events represented such as operator conventions, steward seminars, and other union-related seminars offered on topics including leadership and labor laws. The Local 1112 created many photo albums of conferences and union gatherings;the photos were removed from these albums for preservation purposes, placed in archival-quality photo sleeves, and filed withinthis series where appropriate.
  - Cornell University, Photographs, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 1)
  - 1st Constitutional Convention, Sheraton Motor Inn, Syracuse, N.Y., Photographs, 1975 September (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 2)
  - N.F.I.U. Washington,D.C. Photographs, 1976 March (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 3)
  - 2nd Educational Convention, Ramada Inn, Albany, N.Y., Photographs, 1976 October 13-1976 October 14 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 4)
  - CWA-Annual Conventions, 1978-1983 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 5)
  - TTUU Delegates at T.I.U. Meeting at Atlantic City, N.J., Photograph, 1978 May 01-1978 May 03 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 6)
  - 3rd Educational Convention, Sheraton Inn, Syracause, N.Y., Photographs, 1978 October 16-1978 October 19 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 7)
  - T.T.U.U. Convention, ca. 1970s (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 8)
  - T.I.U. Convention, Wilmington, Delaware, Photographs, 1980 April (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 9)
  - Bargaining Seminar, University of Wisconsin Madison, Photographs, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 10)
  - T.T.U.U. Conventions, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 11)
  - Division Reps Workshop, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 12)
  - Telephone Traffic Union Seminar, Utica, N.Y., Photographs, 1983 February (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 13)
  - CWA Annual Convention, 1984 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 14)
  - TIU Convention, Photographs, 1984 July 25 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 15)
  - Seminar, Niagara Hilton, Photographs, ca. 1984 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 16)
  - Special Conventions, ca. 1984-1985 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 17)
  - CWA-48th Annual Convention, 1986 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 18-19)
  - Operators Conference, 1986 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 20)
  - CWA-49th Annual Convention, 1987 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 21-22)
  - CWA-50th Annual Convention, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 23)
  - Seminar Photographs, 1988 January (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 24)
  - Women's Conference Photographs, University of Wisconsin, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 25)
  - CWA-50th Annual Convention, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 26-27)
  - CWA-Seminar, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 28-30)
  - Operators United, Photographs, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 31)
  - CWA-51st Annual Convention, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 32-33)
  - CWA-Seminar, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 34-36)
  - Stewards Seminar, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 1)
  - CWA-52nd Annual Convention, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 2-4)
  - CWA-District I Leadership Conference, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 5)
  - Labor Law Seminar, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 6)
  - Operators Conference, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 7)
  - CWA-53rd Annual Convention, 1991 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 8-12)
  - CWA/AT&T Leadership Conference, 1991 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 13)
  - Communications and Technologies Annual Leadership Conference, 1991 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 14-15)
  - Milwaukee Conference, 1991 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 16)
  - Operators Conference, 1991 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 17)
  - T.T.U.U. Convention, 1992 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 18)
  - AT&T Leadership Conference, 1992 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 19)
  - CWA 54th Annual Convention (1-4 of 5), 1992 (Box 2 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 20-23)
  - CWA 54th Annual Convention (5 of 5), 1992 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 1)
  - CWA District I Conference, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 2)
  - CWA--Seminar, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 3)
  - Local 1112 Stewards' Educational Seminar, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 4)
  - Operators Conference, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 5)
  - Stewards Seminar, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 6)
  - CWA 55th Annual Convention, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 7-8)
  - CWA-District I Leadership Conference, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 9)
  - CCWA-56th Annual Convention, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 10-11)
  - CWA-57th Annual Convention, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 12)
  - CWA-Seminar, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 13-15)
  - Stewards Seminar, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 16)
  - CWA-58th Annual Convention, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 17-19)
  - CWA-59th Annual Convention (1-2 of 3), 1997 (Box 3 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 20-21)
  - CWA-59th Annual Convention (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 4 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 1)
  - CWA-60th Annual Convention, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 2-3)
  - Operators Conference, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 4)
  - CWA-61st Annual Convention, 1999 (Box 4 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 5-6)
  - CWA-62nd Annual Convention, 2000 (Box 4 (5-Conventions and Seminars), Folder 7-8)
- Membership Files - [RESTRICTED], 1975-2001 (Bulk 1983-1999); Undated; 6; 5.8 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically in Subseries 1, then by case number for Subseries 2 and 3.
  These materials are divided into three subseries--membership services, local grievances, and National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) grievances. The first subseries has information about retirements, applications for union membership, and daily problems that needed supervisory intervention but were not serious enough to warrant actual grievance procedure. Local grievances included, but are not limited to, issues such as dismissal for poor attendance, need for lengthy sick leave, and wage discrepancies. NLRB cases are more of a mixture of individual cases as well as cases where the entire local chose to grieve an issue on behalf of all its members.
  Please note that these files contain individual member information of a sensitive nature and are therefore restricted. Researchers seeking access to these materials should contact the head of archives.
  - Membership Services, 1975-1998; 6.1
    - Absence for Union Business Monthly Reports, 1981-1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Absence for Union Business Monthly Reports, 1987-1992 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - AT&T Surplus, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - AT&T Surplus, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - AT&T Temps '92/'93, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - CWA Retiree Card Applications, 1989-1992; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Dues Authorization and Membership Application Cards, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Dues Authorization and Membership Application Cards, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Dues Authorization and Membership Application Cards, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9-10)
    - Dues Authorization and Membership Application Cards, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11-12)
    - Dues Authorization and Membership Application Cards, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Gates McDonald, 1993-1996; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Offices, Albany Member Issues, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Offices, Amherst Member Issues, 1988-1993; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Offices, Amherst Member Issues, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Offices, Amherst Member Issues, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Offices, Amherst Office Closing, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Offices, Binghamton Deferred Vested Pension, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Offices, Binghamton Member Issues, 1991-1995; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Offices, Syracuse Alliance Funding, 1993; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Offices, Syracuse Member Issues, 1984-1985; 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Offices, Utica Member Issues, 1987; 1991-1995; Undated (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Resignations, 1975; 1977; 1979; 1981-1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Resignations, 1986-1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Resignations, 1989-1992 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Resignations, 1992-1997 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Retired or Deceased List from 1/1/75 and 10/20/76, Undated (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - UCAT Cases, Undated (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Local Grievances, 1980-1999; 6.2
    - Grievance #975, Brucklier, Page, Ventura and R. Harris, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Grievance #2073, J. Herczak, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2-5)
    - Grievance #7210-7214, S. Gurdo and C. Staggs, 1987-1989; 1991 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6-7)
    - Grievance #7218-7219, S. Gurdo and C. Staggs, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Grievance #7237, C. Bradford, 1980-1984 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9-11)
    - Grievance #8262, 8264, 8265 J. Kenyon, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Grievance #8262, 8264, 8265 J. Kenyon, 1982; 1991-1993; 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Grievance #8745, E. Cassidy, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14-15)
    - Grievance #8749, E. Cassidy, 1991-1996 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16-17)
    - Grievance #8819, Special Leave Program (SLP) Participants (1-2 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18-19)
    - Grievance #8819, Special Leave Program (SLP) Participants (3-4 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1-2)
    - Grievance #8862, J. Zielinski, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Grievance #8863, G. Teal, 1995-1997 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Grievance #8866, D. Allen, 1992-1994; 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Grievance #8867, S. Giroux, 1992-1997 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Grievance #8868, D. Angilletta, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Grievance #8870, R. Harold, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Grievance #8871 and #8872, K. Sears, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Grievance #8873, K. Sears, 1994-1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2-3)
    - Grievance #9051, C. Mitchell, 1992-1994 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4-5)
    - Grievance #9075, W. Decker, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Grievance #9076, D. Thomas, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Grievance #9997, D. Grimes, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Grievance #9998, C. Johnson, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Grievance #9999, B. Kelly, 1989-1992 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Typing Test Results Case, 1991 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - National Labor Relations Board Grievances, 1984-2001; 6.3
    - AT&T--SIY, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Button vs. NYNEX, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Case #1-87-8L, H. Hug, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Case #05B-19684-95, N. Nigro, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Case #11B-22293-95, K. Ganance, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Case #86-CV-0563E, New York Telephone vs. Telephone Traffic Union, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6-8)
    - Case #87-CV-1437, C.J. Munson, 1988; 1992 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Case #90-C-0191, Order Determining Revenue Requirement and Rate Design, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Case #90-CV-906, Zawilinski, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Case #5216-89, Order to Show Cause, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Case #3CA-12485 and #3CA-12614, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13-14)
    - Case #3CA-13161, C. Morton, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Case #3CA-12522-2, J. DiMaina, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Case #3CA-12614, AT&T Northeast Region, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Case #3CA-13287, S. Bobak, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Case #3CA-13288, C. Morton, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Case #3CA-13292 S. Ross, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Case #3CA-13301 J. Blaszczak, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Case #3CA-13303, J. Blaszczak, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Case #3CA-13349, Seabrooke Unit, Utica, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Case #3CA-13395, J. Dimaina, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Case #3CA-13909, C. Stables, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Case #3CA-14379, K. Waugh, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Case #3CA-14410 et. al. K. Waugh and J. Dimaina, etc., 1988 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Case #3Ca-14410, J. Dimaina, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Case #3CA-14431, K. Van Every, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Case #3CA-14177, C. Ferrare, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 130container)
    - Case #3CA-14700, J. Dimaina, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Case #3CA-15018, C. Ferrare, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
    - Case #3CA-15167, New York Telephone, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
    - Case #3CA-15383, J. Ferrare, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
    - Case #3CA-15414, Siller and Martin, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
    - Case #3CA-15516, Unfair Labor Practice, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
    - Case #3CA-15660, Rowe, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
    - Case #3CA-15661, G. Perratta, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
    - Case #3CA-15677, Manual Selection of Hours, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
    - Case #3CA-15961, M. Stanley, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
    - Case #3CA-16564, Catskill Office, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
    - Case #3CA-16951, D. Stangle, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
    - Case #3CA-16972, L. Vincent, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
    - Case #3CA-17101, Unfair Labor Practice, Clifton Park, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
    - Case #3CA-17295, L. Vincent, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
    - Case #3CA-18224, K. Young, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
    - Case #3CA-18303, D. Molinaro, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
    - Case #3CA-19718, AT&T Refusal to Provide Requested Information, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
    - Case #3CA-19868, Failure to Bargain Collectively, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
    - Case #3CA-20153, E. Kluczynski, 1996; 2001 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
    - Case #3CA-20154, Failure to Bargain Collectively, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
    - Case #3CA-20257, Failure to Bargain Collectively, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
    - Case #3CA-20375, Elmira Office, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
    - Case #3CA-20378, Revocation of Settlement Agreement, etc., 1996-1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 54)
    - Case #3CA-20886, Clifton Park Relay Service, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 55)
    - Case #3CA-20906, Revocation of Settlement Agreement, etc., 1997-1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 56)
    - Case #3CA-20908, Failure to Provide Requested Information, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 57)
    - Case #3CA-21082, New York Telephone/Bell Atlantic, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 58)
    - Case #3CA-21178, Unfair Labor Practice, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 59)
    - Case #3CA-21240, Clerical, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 60)
    - Case #3CA-21285, N. Knight, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 61)
    - Case #3CA-21432, Bell Atlantic, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 62)
    - Case #3CA-21525, Incidental Absence, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 63)
    - Case #3CA-21586, D. Baird, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 64)
    - Case #3CA-21591, Lawful vs. Unlawful Assistance, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 65)
    - Case #3CA-21621, Failure to Bargain Collectively, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 66)
    - Case #3CA-21983, Failure to Bargain Collectively, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 67)
    - Case #3CA-22288, Reese and Rockwell, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 68)
    - Case #3CA-22452, Troy, New York N.A.C. Office, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 69)
    - Case#3CA-22455 and 22461, Failure to Bargain Collectively, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Case #3CA-22601-1, Unlawful Suspensions, 2000 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Case #3CB-4413, et. al. K. Baron, 1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Case #3CB-4705, J.Crane, 1985 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Case #3CB-4750, National Labor Relations Act, Section 7, 1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Case #3CB-4750, R. Marrara, 1985 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Case #3CB-4750, R. Marrara, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Case #3CB-4926-2, Picketing Issue, 1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Case #3CB-4945 et. al., G. Fobes, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Case #3CB-4945, 4946, 4951 to 4953, 1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - 11. Case #3CB-4953, E. Conway, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Case #3CB-4954, G. Dubel, 1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Case #3CB-4954-2, A. Perry, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Case #3CB-5031, C. Dancesia, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Case #3CB-5077, S. Smallwood, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Case #3CB-5089, N. Barlette, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Case #3CB-5449, M. Jacobs, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Case #3CB-5511, E. Conway, 1989-1991 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Case #3CB-5526, M. Green, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Case #3CB-5536, S. Gowett, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Case #3CB-5538, A. Topor, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Case #3CB-5539, R. Doxtader, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Case #3CB-5540, S. Orilio, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Case #3CB-5548, G. Fobes, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Case #3CB-5549, W. Fobes, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25-26)
    - Case #3CB-5554, C. Schermerhorn, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Case #3CB-5556, L. DiBerdino, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Case #3CB-5580, A. Harrington, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Case #3CB-5638/(c)3CA-15467, Conroy, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    - 31. Case #3CB-5814, H. Siller, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Case #3CB-6257, H. Baldwin, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
    - Case #3CB-6602, C.A. Collins, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
    - Case #3CB-6898, D. Evans, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
    - Case #3CB-7078, R. Parker, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
    - Case #3CB-7711-1, K. Carson vs. Local 1112, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
    - 37. Case #3CC-1360 and 1362, Unfair Labor Practice, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
    - Charge Against Employer, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
    - Charge Against Employer/Union Bulletin Board Postings, 1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)